Lev Koganov

Full-Stack Developer

<u>Phone</u>: 050-5201472 <u>Email</u>: levkoganov.dev@gmail.com <u>Location</u>: Israel - Ashdod <u>LinkedIn</u>: <u>linkedin.com/lev</u> <u>Portfolio</u>: <u>lev-koganov-website</u> <u>GitHub</u>: <u>github.com/Lev</u>

I'm a Full Stack Developer with 3 years of hands-on experience designing, developing, and implementing applications and solutions using a range of technologies and programming languages.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Matrix (2023)

Frontend - Developer

Developed an interface from scratch for a Bank clearing center. Worked on a tight schedule according to specification.

- Frontend technologies. (React | Typescript | Mobx | Figma | KandoUI)
- Integrations and Environments. (Python | Gitlab | Git | Jira | Nginx)

Wizdome (2022 – 2023)

Fullstack - Developer

Developed a user interface for a cyber security company. Integrating with a complex cyber security engine that warns and prevent security breaches.

- Frontend technologies. (React | Typescript | Redux | Figma)
- Backend and Database. (Node.JS | MongoDB)
- Integrations and Environments. (GitHub | Git | Jira | AWS | Docker | Linux)

PlaySmart (2021 – 2022)

Fullstack – Developer

Developed a web gaming system from scratch using a high variety of technologies. Worked closely with the CRM team, implementing web services, creating an interactive interface and REST API.

- Frontend technologies. (JavaScript | JQuery)
- Backend & Database. (Node.JS | PHP | MongoDB | MySQL)
- Integrations and Environments. (WordPress | C#.NET | Bitbucket | Jira)

INTEL (2018 – 2019)

Service Engineer

- Assembling production machines inside a clean room.
- Post assembly machine modification, calibration, validating machine.

EDUCATION

Real Time Collage (2019 – 2021)

Diploma – Full stack Developer

MILITARY SERVICE

Military Police (2014 – 2017)

Imprisoned accompaniers and guarding inmates between prisons and outdoor activities.

Languages: Hebrew – Native | English – Fluent | Russian – Fluent